{
    "Qstns": [
        {
            "questionText": "It is the exchange of thoughts, messages, or information as by speech, signals, writing or behavior.",
            "option1": "communication",
            "option2": "feedback",
            "option3": "language",
            "option4": "message",
            
            "answer":"communication"
        },
        {
            "questionText": "These are considered forms of communication. [1. talking clearly, 2. chewing gum, 3. sending email, 4. looking bored].",
            "option1": "1234",
            "option2": "134 only",
            "option3": "342 only",
            "option4": "1 only",

            "answer": "134 only"
        },
        {
            "questionText": "This body language shows that one is listening.",
            "option1": "nodding and making eye contact",
            "option2": "looking out of the window",
            "option3": "turning away from  the speaker ",
            "option4": "whistling while biting nails",

            "answer": "nodding and making eye contact"
        },
        {
            "questionText": "It is the sender of the message.",
            "option1": "barrier",
            "option2": "originator",
            "option3": "receiver",
            "option4": "sender",

            "answer": "sender"
        },
        {
            "questionText": "It is a good indication that good communication occurs.",
            "option1": "destructed",
            "option2": "confused",
            "option3": "unreceived",
            "option4": "shared",

            "answer": "shared"
        },
        {
            "questionText": "This is the BEST way to continue communication.",
            "option1": "active listening",
            "option2": "asking questions",
            "option3": "not interrupting",
            "option4": "making good eye contact",

            "answer": "active listening"
        },
        {
            "questionText": "It is known when the receiver gives a verbal or non-verbal message.",
            "option1": "answer",
            "option2": "feedback",
            "option3": "response",
            "option4": "none given",

            "answer": "feedback"
        },
        {
            "questionText": " This is to be avoided for effective communication.",
            "option1": "ambiguity",
            "option2": "listening",
            "option3": "politeness",
            "option4": "sharing of activity",

            "answer": "ambiguity"
        },
        {
            "questionText": " This is essential to an effective communication.",
            "option1": "three-way process",
            "option2": "both a one-way and a two-way process",
            "option3": "one-way process",
            "option4": "two-way process",

            "answer": "two-way process"
        },
        {
            "questionText": "This refers to the responsibility of the person who receives the message for communication to take place.",
            "option1": "feedback",
            "option2": "non-verbal clues",
            "option3": "perception",
            "option4": "self-concept",

            "answer": "perception"
        },
        {
            "questionText": "There will be order and peace in the world without communication.",
            "option1": "true",
            "option2": "false",

            "answer": "false"
        },
        {
            "questionText": "Along with the extensive revamp in most aspects of human life, ways of communication also change.",
            "option1": "true",
            "option2": "false",

            "answer": "true"
        },
        {
            "questionText": "Schramm Model is the most complicated example of human communication process.",
            "option1": "true",
            "option2": "false",

            "answer": "false"
        },
        {
            "questionText": "In the interaction model, communication is a one-way process.",
            "option1": "true",
            "option2": "false",

            "answer": "false"
        },
        {
            "questionText": "Communication is merely successful when conflict was absent in the process.",
            "option1": "true",
            "option2": "false",

            "answer": "true"
        },
        {
            "questionText": "Press next to finish the quiz",
    
            "answer": "Yes"
        }
    ]
}